export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "What is the correct command to create a new React project?",
        options:[ "npx create-react-app appname", "npm install create-react-app", "npx install create-react-app -g", "install - l create-react-app"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        options:["Create", "Extends", "Inherits", "Delete"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        options: ["3000", "8080", "5000", "3030"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following valid component return type of React ?",
        options: ["2", "5", "1", "3"],
        answer:3
    },{
        question: "Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        options: ["State & Props", "Services & Components", "State & Services", "State & Component"],
        answer:1
    },{
        question: "What year was JavaScript launched?",
        options: ["1996", "1995", "1994", "none of the above"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
        options: ["Compiler", "Transpilar", "Both of the above", "none of the above"],
        answer:3
    },{
        question: "Which of the following is used to render components in web pages ?",
        options: ["DOM_render()", "render()", "ReactDOM_render()", "transfer()"],
        answer:2
    }
    ,{
        question: "Which of the following is true about key props ?",
        options: ["'Key' props are used to look beauty", "'Key' prop is a way to identify the newly added element", "It is one type of attribute of HTML", "It is not used in the array"],
        answer:2
    }
    ,{
        question: "What is the best definition of React.js ?",
        options: ["Server-side Framework", "User-interface framework", "A Library for building interaction interfaces", "None of These"],
        answer:3
    }
];